我们刚到
we just **
对
year
孩子还好吧?
****in
好
good
对 对 他十分激动
year year****
嗨 听着 我得挂了
look,I gotta go,ok?
明天打给你
I'll call you tomorrow
让一让
exucuse me
走开 走开
get away get away
不好意思 对不起
sorry about that,sorry
他怎么了?
what's wrong whit them?
让一让
excuse us
真想过去好好教训下他
*go back*******
她年纪不小了 没必要叫成那样
She's old enough.She didn't/have to scream like that.
没事的 爸爸 我没不高兴
It's okay,dad.It didn't bother me.
第一次感觉到/他们无法影响我心情
For the first time,none/of these people bother me.
我只是在想36个小时之后
I just think--36/more hours.
Kenny 36个小时怎么算出来的?
36 more hours.How do/you figure that,kenny?
手术安排在明天的这个时候
Tomorrow at this time,i'm/scheduled for surgery.
十小时的手术/加上准备的两小时
It's a ten-hour procedure,throw/two in it for prep.
36个小时之后我就和众人一样了
36 until I'm just/another face in the crowd.
Kenny的病叫额鼻部脑膨出
Kenny has a frontonasal encephalocele.
是颅中线畸形
It's a midline deformity.
他来这里做颅面裂修补术
He's here to undergo a facial bipartion.
那是什么意思
And what does that mean?
我们有五个外科医生 四个护士
Well,we have five surgeons,four nurses.
- 还需要六个单位的血/- 会治好他吗?
- It's going to require 6 units of blood./- Will it fix him?
- 这会修复大部分的损伤/- 我们需要原声播放
- It'll repair a lot of the damage done by/- We need a sound bite.
可否说他能在毕业舞会前康复?
Would you say he'll be/ready for the junior prom?
这也许是可以的
Yeah,yeah.That's probably true.
不 我是说要你来说这句话
No,I mean I need you to say it.
Chase医生 有问题
Dr. Chase.We got an issue.
心跳急速上升 超过180次每分
Heart rate's sky/rocketing.He's over 180.
- 心室纤颤/- 准备电击
- He's in/v-fib. - Paddles.
充电到300焦 把摄像机关掉!
Charge to 300.Turn that camera off.
- 麻醉的不良反应吗?/- 还没麻醉
- Is this a reaction to anesthesia?/- Haven't given it yet.
走开!
Clear.
充电至360焦
Crank it to 360.
我说把那该死的摄像机关掉!
I said turn that damn camera off!
走开
Clear.
患有颅面畸形的少年
A teenage boy with a/cranial facial deformity was
在接受颅面重建的手术的时候
about to undergo
出现了无法解释的心脏骤停
a reconstructive procedure when he/had an unexplained cardiac arrest.
好极了
Good.
好极了?
Good?
我的意思是 继续
I mean,go on.
现在对病人使用心脏起搏器
We have the patient on a pacing wire.
否则心脏将停跳
It's the only thing/keeping his heart going.
我们知道 我们是医生
Yeah,we know.We're doctors.
是的 这是解释给观众听的
Right. It w-was...Just for them.
就你平时的样子就可以了
Just be yourself.
除非我们能够准确找到
Until we are able to figure out
是什么原因造成了心脏传导阻滞
exactly what is causing the heart block,
显然 面部重建手术将暂缓
the reconstructive surgery/is on hold,obviously.
那是平时的你?
That's yourself?
多好的病例
Fascinating case.
我救了他的命之后会再与你见面的
I will see you again after/I have saved his life.
花不了多少时间的
Have a warm bath waiting.
你们是在跟着我吗?
Are you following me?
Darnell会在病例中从头到尾跟着你
Darnell will be trailing/you throughout the case.
就当我们不存在
Pretend we're not here.
如果真当你们不存在 不会撞到你们吗?
If I do that,won't I bump into you?
我们不会碍着你走路的
We'll stay out of your way.
开玩笑呢
That's a joke.
我因为这部电影立志当医生
See,I became a doctor because/of the moviepatch adams.
你们先出去好吗?
Uh,listen,y/- you wanna get ahead of me?
可以退着走/我不知道 也许仰拍?
Maybe back up,I don't know,low down,
让我显得高大一点
so I look more powerful?
- 那太好了/- 真的吗?
- That's perfect./- Yeah?
在夏日的光彩下的房间里/我的眼睛会看起来更漂亮
Also my eyes look better/in rooms with summer colors.
你知道吗 这是黑白片
You know what?It's black and white
你以为我喜欢被采访吗?
You think I likethe cameras?
你认为我想整个世界看你/盯着我的屁股不放?
You think I want the whole world/watching you check out my ass
质疑我的衣柜?
and question my wardrobe?
如果我盯着你的衣柜/并质疑你的屁股呢?
Would it be better if I checked out/your wardrobe and questioned your ass?
- 我有小小的.../- 你哪里都不小呀
- A little part of me/- There is no little part of you.
小小的幻想 以为你懂得
Thought that maybe you would see
医院可以借此提高声誉
what great p.r. This/could be for the hospital,
不用我强制你成个人样
and not make me force you/to act like a human being.
你的强制倒是值得一试
You using force on me is intriguing.
但是摄像机让每个人都成了演员
On the other hand,cameras/make people act.
有的人演得还算正常/有的人表现怪异
Sometimes like human/beings.Sometimes just weird.
有的人穿上激突的内衣
Sometimes they wear open-tip bras.
那是冻得
It's cold in here.
另一个不醒目的问题是/我需要我的小组
A less obvious point/is that I need my team
摆脱镜头前出丑的压力
to be unafraid of the metaphorical fart.
制片方负担这孩子的医药费
That production company is covering/all the medical costs for this kid.
所以要么你就让他们继续拍摄
So either you let them continue filming,
要么你就让这孩子老样子回去
or the kid goes home with the same face.
不好意思
Sorry about that.
私下问的 她...
Private.She,um...
每月除一次唇须
Waxes her moustache once a month and...
容易产生须根内生的问题...
Sometimes gets some pretty/gnarly ingrown hairs.
他雇了你吗?
So did he hire you flat out,
还是跟我们竞争职位?
or are you competing/for one of the spots?
我不知道你说的什么意思
I'm not sure what you mean by that.
她不是来竞争的
She's not competing.
她是Hosue亲手挑的
She was hand-picked by house.
她安全的很 跟Foreman一样
She's safe,like foreman.
现在三个位子只剩下一个了
So that takes three spots down to one.
Foreman哪去了?
Where's foreman?
- 他在厕所/- 好极了 我们出去走走
- He's in the bathroom./- Good. Come on.Let's go for a walk.
在镜头下走显得更帅气
Walks look good on camera.
给观众一种故事发展的映像
They give the illusion of/the story moving forward.
新病人 16岁男孩
New patient.16-year-old/boy with second degree
心脏骤停后出现2度节下传导阻滞
infranodal heart block post-arrest.
有没有发飘或者眩晕的现象
Any reports of/lightheadedness or syncope?
- 他的头不可能飘/- 你为什么雇她
- It's really not lightheadedness./- Why did you hire her?
- 在电视台面前不讨论此事/- 我们会上电视吗?
- Not in front of the company./- Are we gonna be on tv?
我正在制作一个音乐录影带/来吧 快点
I'm making a music/video.Come on,a little faster.
- 劲爆一些!/- 为什么Foreman不在你反而高兴
- More energy./- Why are you glad foreman's not here?
因为他会反对我做的一切
Because he would object/to what I'm about to do.
哦...
Oh...
危险! 限制进入!
Danger! Restricied Access
不允许金属物品靠近强磁场
No Metal Allowed strong Magenetic Field
对不起啦
Sorry
嘿 老兄
Hey,buddy.
不用管我们/我们在此保证他不再乱动
You stay in there.We'll be out here/making sure he doesn't move again.
上帝啊! 终于可以让自己思考了!
God! Finally hear myself think.
- 我们的病人/- 你为什么雇她?
- Our patient/- Why did you hire her?
因为她比我正考虑的泳衣模特
Because she has way more/diagnostic experience
有更多的诊疗经验
than the other swimsuit/models I was considering.
病人患有额鼻部脑膨出伴有中线颅裂
Our patient has a frontonasal/encephalocele with a midline cleft.
别直视看他
Don't stare directly at it.
那是什么造成了大头的心跳停止呢?
So what caused big head's heart to stop?
简单 他的大头
Simple--/his big head.
颅内压升高可能导致心传导阻滞
Increased intracranial pressure/would cause heart block.
错 不可能16年一直查不出
Wrong,16 years they've been/testing that insane noggin to death.
会不会是先天性心脏畸形
What about a congenital heart defec
他头上中线畸形
he has a midline anomaly on his head.
或许心脏中线也有异常
Makes sense he'd have a midline/anomaly in his heart too.
16年来一直没查到?
That 16 years of testing didn't show?
为什么这么晚才加她? 这不公平!
Why did you bring her/in so late?It's not fair.
- 我们.../- 嘿嘿 你要平等
- The rest of us/- Hey,hey,you wanted fair,
那你就选错了工作
you picked the wrong job.
选错了专业
The wrong profession.
选错了物种
The wrong species.
不要管畸形 把病人当一个很丑/很丑的孩子来诊断
Forget the deformity.Treat the patient/like he's any other really,really ugly kid.
感染可以引起心内膜炎
Infection could be endocarditis.
恩 他没有做过人工瓣膜
Well,since he doesn't have/a prosthetic heart valve,
你怀疑他静脉注射毒品
I assume you're thinking/he's an iv drug user?
House说假设他是正常人
House said assume he's normal.
毒贩又不会问他要身份证/也不在乎他长什么样
Dealers don't ask for i.d. And/don't care what you look like.
很好 你说对了他的爱好
Nice. You're right about the habit.
但没说对毒品
You're wrong about the substance.
鼻下皮肤变黑
Blackened skin under the nose
是吸入氟利昂造成的冻伤
equals frostbite from huffing freon.
氟利昂有毒 会损害心脏
Freon's toxic.Damages the heart.
变色可能是黑棘皮症
Discoloration could be/acanthosis nigricans.
这类畸形中常见的并发症
It's a common side effect/of these deformities.
面颊和前额也有变色
There's also discoloration/on the cheeks and forehead.
做一个核素扫描
Do a nuclear study.
如果我对了 就可以看到心脏瘢痕
If I'm right,you'll see/scarring of the heart.
我不必参加什么游戏吧?
I'm not part of some game,am i?
我辞去了工作/因为我认为这个职位是我的
I gave up a career because I/thought this was a firm offer.
对 这个职位是你的
Yes.This is a real offer.
- 她可能是个白痴/- 谁?
- I think she might be an idiot./- Who?
她不可能是个白痴啊
She can't be an idiot.
看在上帝的份上 她在中央情报局干过
She was in the cia,for god's sake.
猪湾行动是一次大胜利/(CIA在古巴策动的一次惨败)
The bay of pigs was a daring triumph.
她在CIA总部里见解独到
She had good ideas in langley.
全是你的见解
All your ideas.
她能辨别出那是好的见解
She was able to identify/that they were good ideas.
我胡乱问一句 她漂亮吗?
Stab in the dark here.Is she pretty?
她是新人 她很害羞
She's new.She's nervous.
- 她有C罩杯/- 她只是给了一个很蠢的诊断
- She's a "c" cup./- She said one dumb thing in a differential.
人人都会说蠢话
They all say dumb/things in differentials.
D罩杯?
A "d" cup?
她不够好 炒了她
She's no good.Just fire her.
我不能
I can't.
我才雇了她
I just hired her.
她放弃公职的
She left a career.
哇
Wow.
你的内疚不像假装的
You know,that's actual guilt,
我真得见见这个女人了
or I've got to see this woman.
我的儿子没有吸氟利昂
My son is not huffing freon.
Arnold先生 House医生是专家
Mr. Arnold,Dr. House is like a savant
在诊断方面
when it comes to diagnostics.
那他的高论呢?
What's his genius theory?
因为Kenny不正常
Because kenny's not normal,
他用毒品麻醉自己的伤痛?
he's doing drugs to deal with his pain?
我们换个角度看 你很正常
Maybe the way to look at/this is that you are normal.
这是什么意思?
And what's that supposed to mean?
你就像其他的父母一样
You're like any other parent
认为自己的孩子不会吸毒
who thinks his kid can't be doing drugs.
我们做这个是因为我爸怀疑我吸毒
We're doing this 'cause/my dad thinks I'm on drugs?
在你这么大的时候我也吸毒/而且我有很多的理由
I was doing drugs behind my parents' back at/your age,and I had a lot less reason to be--
我不是说你生活一定很痛苦
Not that your life must be miserable.
我没有支持吸毒
Not that I'm suggesting that/you should be doing drugs.
- 学校怎么样?/- 我在家学习
- How's school going?/- I'm homeschooled.
真的吗?
Really?
你真幸运
You're lucky.
去学校太无聊了
Going to school was boring.
我爸把我从学校带回来/不是因为学校很无聊
My dad took me out,and it/wasn't 'cause it was boring.
我在学校日子也过得很难
Well,I had a rough time in school too.
也许不像你 但是..
Maybe not like you,but,uh...
你知道 我的意思是/我不想比较我们两人的处境
You know,I mean,I don't mean/to compare our situations.
其实 我是在比较我们的情况
Actually,I guess I am/comparing our situations,
但只是让你明白了自己有多糟糕
but only to show you how yours is worse.
你能把那句删掉对吧？/我不想像个白痴似的
You can edit that out,right?So/I don't look like an idiot.
别紧张 人人在我身边都会变的像白痴
Relax. Everyone acts/like an idiot around me.
行为举止就像演戏一样 你不觉得吗?
What makes you think it's not an act?
- 头好疼 有药吗?/- 有 这是新症状?
- Can I have something for my headache?/- Yeah. Is that new?
疼了16年
16 years old.
从生下来那天开始
Has the same birthday I do.
我这就去检查
I'm gonna start the test now.
结果出来了 没有心脏瘢痕
Study showed no signs of/scarring in kenny's heart.
不是毒品问题
It wasn't drugs.
还有好点的解释吗?
Well,then give me something better?
什么导致了心脏传导阻滞?
What's causing heart block?
可能是弓形体病/应该做个腰穿检查感染
Could be toxoplasmosis.We should/do an lp to test for infection.
如果是弓形体病/应该会出现淋巴肿大
If it was toxoplasmosis,we/would have seen enlarged lymphs.
既然你没漂亮到当花瓶的程度/你肯定也明白这一点
And because you're not pretty enough to/be an idiot,you must know that already.
也就是说你做LP的目的是查颅内压
Which means you just said it because you wanna/do an lp to look for intracranial pressure.
- 因为正是颅内压/- 等等 我还没说完
- Because it is intracranial pressure./- Wait. I'm not done.
你本以为我会不明白你的意图
You thought I wouldn't catch on,
也就是说/要么你觉得我是个白痴花瓶
which means either/you think i'm an idiot,
那倒算是恭维了--/今天我换了个发型--
which is flattering-- I'm/doing my hair differently--
这孩子一直头疼/他吃扑热息痛就像吃花生似的
The kid's got headaches.He's been/popping acetaminophen like peanuts.
你难道以为我已经说完了吗?
How could you possibly/think that I was done?
我前面说了个‘要么’
I prefaced that with an either.
后面就还有个‘要么’/要么
It needs an "or." Or
你是个白痴花瓶--这一点很有可能
you are an idiot--Which/is possible.
我不擅长评价男人的长相
I'm not great at judging men's looks.
在手术室
The o.r.
还有核磁共振室
And the mri room.
是的
Yes.
House医生常常在不同的地方进行鉴别诊断
Dr. House frequently conducts differential/diagnoses in a variety of places.
他觉得...
He feels that a...
环境的变化能带来思路的变化
Change in venue often leads to/a change in thinking processes.
我得去忙别的事了
I have to go take/care of something else.
就让我做个CT扫描吧/看看我的想法对不对
Just let me do a ct/scan,see if I'm right.
问题解决的越早
The sooner we fix the problem,
再造手术就能进行的越早
the sooner we can get to/his reconstructive surgery.
是啊 病人死活你才不管/脸变漂亮最重要
Yeah,who cares if you're/dead?It's how you look.
既然你说不出个理所当然/我们还是回到毒品的思路上
Well,since you've given me/nothing better,we're back to drugs.
毒品是我们唯一可以排除的原因
The one thing we know it's not.
室间隔膜部核素摄取减低
Decreased uptake on/the membranous septum.
可能是显影失真 可以重做一下
Could be an artifact.We can redo it,
但是-- 没有就是没有/做诱发电位检查
but-- Nothing's/nothing.Do an ep study.
做损伤效应研究会让那孩子心脏停跳
Ep study means we have/to stop this kid's heart.
我去准备
I'll set it up.
House
House.
你有空吗? 我要把你开膛破肚！
You have a minute to be disemboweled?
导管会穿过你心脏的不同区域
I'm gonna thread this catheter/through different areas in your heart,
一旦找到正确的路径
and once I've found the right pathway,
我会发出一些电脉冲
i'll apply some electrical energy.
这会让我心脏停跳吗?
It'll stop my heart?
听着很吓人/不过你会没事的
It sounds worse than/it is.You'll be fine.
会疼吗?
Is it gonna hurt?
会有点不舒服
There'll be some discomfort.
如果你吸过毒
If you've done drugs,
我完全理解
I understand.
与众不同是很辛苦的
Being different's really hard.
Kenny 呃...
Kenny,um...
康复才是最重要的
It's more important/for you to get better
不要担心惹麻烦
than to worry about getting in trouble.
如果我吸毒 心脏问题就说的通了?
If I did drugs,that could/explain my heart problem?
是的
It could.
然后就可以动手术治好我的脸?
Then you can do the/surgery to fix my face?
正是如此
That's why we're here.
你知道 那些名人...
You know how famous people...
不管去哪 都有人关注
Everywhere they go,people/are watching them,
众目睽睽
staring?
他们从未有过机会做回自己
They never have a chance to just be.
他们中很多都求助于毒品
You know,and a lot/of them turn to drugs.
他们被人关注是因为美
People stare atthem/because they're beautiful,
而我不是
but me,they just stare.
你还好吧?
You okay?
Kenny 你用什么类型的毒品/用过多少
I need to know what kind/of drugs,kenny,and how much.
恩 可卡因/很多可卡因
Um,coke,mostly.A lot of coke.
要是缺货了
And then,uh,when I run out,
通常我就用lsd或者acid
I usually go to lsd,or,uh,or acid.
这两个是一回事
Those are the same thing.
是吗?
They are?
你不吸毒 对吧?
You don't do drugs,do you?
- 我从老爸的酒柜里偷酒喝/- 测试不用做了
- I drink from my dad's liquor cabinet/- We're not gonna do this test.
侧过身来
I need you to turn on your side.
进行插管! 这里需要抢救!
We need to intubate.I/need some help in here!
可惜你们受分级制度限制
Too bad you guys are going/for a theatrical release.
不然吐血会是多么震撼的一幕啊
Vomiting blood would/have made a great act out.
可能的原因
Likely causes.
- 马洛里-魏斯二氏综合征/- 没有面容苍白 黑粪便等症状
- Mallory-weiss tear./- No pallor,no melena.
你干嘛打领带?
Why are you wearing a tie?
呃 我一直都打领带
Uh,I always wear ties.
我是医生
I'm a doctor.
- 请别注视摄像机/- 抱歉
- Please don't look at the camera./- Sorry.
鼻乳头状瘤 吐血会导致/心脏不胜负荷
Nasal papilloma.Hemorrhage/could have overwhelmed the heart.
口红很美
Nice lipstick.
- 谢谢/- 想法很烂
- Thank you./- Bad idea.
吐血出现在传导阻滞之后
Hemorrhage came after the block.
House 别妨碍他们工作
House,let them do their job.
你们都不关心医学
Anybody here more/interested in the medicine,
只在乎狗仔队吗?
a little less interested/in the paparazzi?
上肠胃道出血
Upper g.i. Bleed.
可能是饮食不当造成的
Could be something he ate or drank.
可能是消化性溃疡
Maybe a peptic ulcer.
很好
Good.
但是没有腹痛的症状
Except no abdominal pain.
病患胃口如常/还有最后一点 据我所知
Patient hasn't lost his/appetite,and the last I checked,
肠胃道和心脏是不相通的
the gastrointestinal tract/isn't connected to the heart.
是的 不过除此以外 想法不错
Yeah. But other than that,real good.
青年鼻咽血管纤维瘤
Nasopharyngeal angiofibrosis.
我刚说了不是鼻部肿瘤
I just said it wasn't a nasal tumor.
胃癌 肿瘤导致吐血
Stomach cancer.Tumor causes bleeding.
肿瘤又导致瘤外综合征
Body's reaction to the tumor/causes paraneoplastic syndrome
进而导致心传导阻滞
which leads to heart block.
谢天谢地!/总算有个聪明又漂亮的人出现了
Finally! Someone who is/not just a pretty face.
你和Taub去做检查 找出肿瘤
You and taub run the/scope,find the tumor.
呃 可能会有危险
Uh,could be dangerous.
如果是颅内压导致了肝衰竭/进而导致吐血--
If the bleeding was caused by liver failure/as the result of the intracranial pressure--
颅内压和肝脏完全不沾边
Liver is the one organ you can't/ascribe to intracranial pressure.
的确
True.
颅内压可能导致肝脏问题
Intracranial pressure/cancause liver problems.
先造成海绵窦压力增大
It causes an increase in/the cavernous sinus pressure
进而对上腔静脉形成压力
which causes pressure/in the superior vena cava
最后导致肝衰竭
which shuts down the liver.
- 你才想到吗?/- 不
- You just think of that?/- no.
- 那你刚刚为什么不辩驳?/- 能改变他的想法吗?不可能
- Then why didn't you say anything/- Think it would change his mind?Not a chance.
House会压住我 让我去做
House would have undercut/me,ordered me to do a procedure
我不认同的检查  然后我会
I just argued against,and/then I'd look like
成为无数观众和潜在雇主眼中的伪君子
a hypocrite in front of the thousands of people/and potential future employers watching this film.
如果你是对的/肝衰竭的孩子做内窥镜检查
If you're right,and we stick a scope/back down a kid with liver failure,
他会再度出血的
he could bleed again.
我知道
I know.
他刚刚吐过血
He just vomited blood.
难道不危险吗?
Isn't that dangerous?
没事 医生们都很有经验
No. You're in good hands.
好
Okay.
好吧
All right.
他从挫折中走出来是很了不起的
Well,it's great how he/rebounded from that setback.
什么挫折?
What setback?
他没跟你说过...
He didn't tell you about the...
好吧 这是他的权利
Well,it's his right.
记录是保密的
Records were sealed.
我个人认为他是在踮着脚
Personally,I think he/was just tapping his foot
去拿厕纸
and reaching for the toilet paper.
很明显 这是在迫害巫师
Obviously,it was a witch hunt.
你觉得他们是因为与House意见相左...
Do you think they/singled him out because...
不 我的意思就是迫害巫师
No,literally a witch hunt.
House医生是执业巫医
Dr. House is a practicing wiccan.
这是很美的信仰
It's a beautiful religion.
很体贴
It's very caring.
嗨 嗨 嗨 嗨!
Hey,hey,hey,hey.
你们可以随心所欲的拍这个病例
You have an all-access/pass to the case,
但不能拍我的小宠物 快走
not my fave five,so go.
快点 快点 走吧
Come on,come on,let's go.
我看我快瞎了
I think I'm going blind.
手上也长毛了?
Hairy palms too?
她又说蠢话了
She said something idiotic again,
我甚至都没注意到
and I didn't even notice it.
Foreman不得不指出那话有多蠢
Foreman had to point/out that it was idiotic.
- 她让我成了白痴/- 真可爱 你迷恋她
- She's makingmean idiot./- That's cute.You have a crush.
不 我觉得没这么简单
No,I think it's something systemic.
13号很漂亮
Thirteen's pretty.
她对你明显没影响
You're obviously okay with her.
她害死了个病人
She killed a patient.
- 贱人很漂亮/- 贱人就是贱人
- The bitch is pretty./- The bitch is a bitch.
- 约她出去/- 贱人? 她可是贱人啊
- Ask her out./- The bitch?She's a bitch.
不 约那个让你变白痴的
No,the one that's making you an idiot.
生命的真谛-- 男孩碰上女孩/男孩变蠢蛋
The story of life-- Boy/meets girl.Boy gets stupid.
他们从此愚天蠢地的生活在一起
Boy and girl live stupidly ever after.
13号美女又害死人了?
Pretty girl kill again?
没有 大象人刚刚又吐血了
Nope. Elephant boy just/vomiting up blood again.
病患胃部无肿瘤 所以--
No tumors in the/patient's stomach,so--
但内窥镜导致静脉破裂
But the scope caused variceal bleeding.
花了20分钟才止住血
Took 20 minutes of banding to stop it.
- Taub说的对 是肝衰竭/- 没错
- Taub was right about the liver failure./- Yeah.
- 他的头骨变形是引起颅内压力的原因/- 不对
- His craniofacial deformity is causing intracranial pressure/- no.
没有鼻血 呼吸也没有粗重
Where are the nose bleeds?Where's/the labored breathing?
你说的对 我是弄错了
You're right about me being wrong.
但你也不是正确的
You're wrong about you being right.
我要新思路
I need new ideas.
谁来说?
Anybody.
你们一点不觉得有愧吗?/这孩子快要死了
Does it bother you that/this kid's gonna die
就因为你们不愿意放下摄像机?
'cause you won't put down/that camera?At all,you know?
这会激发他们的使命感
Your people should be extra motivated.
他们肯定都想在片子表现出好的一面
I'm sure they all wanna/look good in the film.
没有 他们都太担心自己会出错
No,'cause now they're too/worried about looking bad.
House医生 心传导阻滞加上肝衰竭/可能是自身免疫系统的问题
Dr. House,heart block plus liver/failure could mean autoimmune.
也许是硬皮症
Maybe scleroderma.
Foreman 有道理吗?
Foreman,does that make sense?
除非病人手部皮肤变硬
Not without tight skin on the hands,
肌肉虚弱 年龄超过30岁
muscle weakness,and/a 30-year-old patient.
心传导阻滞加上肝衰竭/可能是线粒体障碍疾病
Liver failure plus heart block/could be a mitochondrial disorder.
嗨 把她的话重复一遍
Hey,say what she just said.
心传导阻滞加上肝衰竭/可能是线粒体障碍疾病?
Liver failure plus heart block/could be a mitochondrial disorder?
检查一下有无视网膜变性的症状
Go look for signs of/retinal degeneration.
就是颅内压的问题/你只会看到肿大
No,it's icp.You're/only gonna see swelling.
带上他 让他亲眼见见变性
Take him with you,so he can/see the degeneration too.
你在急诊室工作之前/是为House工作的 对吧?
So before you worked here in the/e.r.,you worked for house,right?
- 三年半/- 为什么不干了?
- Three and a half years./- Why did you leave?
嗨 我不想上电视
Hey,I don't wanna be on tv.
- 我不会同意发行的/- 我们会对你进行模糊处理
- I'm not signing a release./- We'll blur you out.
脱掉裤子
Take off your pants.
要是我说脏字 是不是带子就废了?
You gonna be able to use any/of this if I start swearing?
House对待你就像对待现在的员工一样恶劣吗?
Did house treat you as badly as/he treats his current fellows?
- 很复杂的问题/- 干-哦!
- Loaded question./- Fawwwrk!
这都不能算是一个词
That's not even a word.
- 叉!/- 真聪明
- Fork!/- Very clever.
我从他那里学会了如何当一名医生
I learned how to be a doctor from house.
我已经是合格医生/House让我成为真正的"医者"
Or at least a doctor who learned/how to be a doctor from house,
这么说不知清楚否
if that makes any sense.
你离开了他的团队是因为
Any you left his team because
- 你无法再忍受他了吗?/- 不 不
- you couldn't stand him anymore?/- No,no.
我...我爱House医生
I...i love Dr. House.
那可是我们没听过的事情
That's something we haven't heard.
我的意思是...
I mean...
- 你刚才问我什么来着?/- 你为什么离开
- What did you ask me again?/- Why you left.
我...我喜欢在他周围...
I...i loved being around him...
我是说职业上的
Professionally,you know.
总是能...刺激你
It was always...Stimulating.
不是一个色情的词汇
Not in an erotic sense of the word.
叉子 他们先来叉式 然后又玩勺式
Fork.They forked.And then they spooned.
向前倾斜然后把你的下巴靠在上面
Lean forward and place/your chin on the rest.
我够不着
I can't reach it.
呃 往前面挪一点
Uh,scooch in a little.
让我来处理吧
I'll take care of it.
就像上一次那样吗?
Just like last time?
也许我们应该试试这种老方法
Maybe we should try this/the old-fashioned way,hmm?
好的 看着上面的天花板/尽量不要眨眼睛 好吗?
Okay,look up to the ceiling/and try not to blink,okay?
好的 很好 现在看着正前方
Okay,good.Now straight ahead.
找到了
There it is.
是肿胀 不是脑变性
Swelling.No degeneration.
不是线粒体障碍疾病/是他的颅内压升高
It's not mitochondrial.Swelling proves/there's increased pressure in his brain.
当然
Absolutely.
那么我们现在可以确定/面部修复手术的时间了
So now we can schedule/the reconstruction.
当然不可以
Absolutely not.
你的检查证明了你是错的
Your test proved you wrong.
我们精确地发现了我之前所预测的
We found exactly what/I predicted we'd find.
肿胀意味着颅内压升高
Swelling means there's/increased pressure.
给你发一个金色六芒星
You get a gold star of/david for proving that,
因为你证明了他子有个大脑袋/而大脑袋引起了颅内压升高
yes,this kid has a big head,and/big heads cause pressure.
但是那不能解释他的肝脏问题
But it doesn't explain the liver.
可以用头疼药过量解释
Too much acetaminophen does.
青少年类风湿关节炎/解释一切 包括肝脏
Jra explains all of/it,including the liver.
解释越简约越好/用类固醇治疗
One theory's better than/two.Treat with steroids.
如果你是错的/类固醇就会破坏他的免疫系统
If you're wrong,steroids are/gonna mess with his immune system,
以致他的外科手术被延期数月之久
put off his surgery for months.
你真的想在摄像机面前争论失败吗?
You really wanna lose this/argument in front of the camera?
我去跟他父亲谈谈
I'll speak to the father.
House医生相信kenny患有JRA
Dr. House believes that kenny has jra,
青少年类风湿性关节炎
juvenile rheumatoid arthritis.
我们需要开始用类固醇来治疗
We need to start administering steroids.
类固醇能治好他吗?
Will the steroids fix it?
我不认为他有JRA
I don't think he has jra.
我认为House医生的判断是错误的
I think Dr. House is wrong
而且类固醇治疗可能会很危险
and that the steroid/treatment could be dangerous.
我想我可以让House撤手这个病例
I think I can get house/thrown off the case,
并给kenny做面部整形手术
and get kenny the/facial surgery he needs.
孩子的父亲拒绝使用类固醇/除非我们能确定诊断结果
The father refused steroids until/we're sure about the diagnosis.
我很确定
I am sure.
那是JRA
It's jra.
而且他为什么会怀疑呢
And why would he even doubt that,
除非我们这里有一个老家伙/在他的耳边说了什么
unless a former fellow of/mine was chirping in his ear.
决定权在他那里
The decision was his.
我只不过表达了我的关心
I merely voiced my concern.
你为什么想要这份工作?
Why'd you take this job?
他有一个膨出性囊肿
He's got a bulging cyst.
你干整形医生非常赚钱
You had a perfectly good plastic/surgery practice,lots of money.
液体没有排出
Fluids aren't draining properly.
莫非你主要的兴趣 是给我捣乱?
Temptation to come screw/with me just too much for you?
肯定有深层理由
There's gotta be a better reason.
他需要手术来排出
He needs surgery to drain it.
噢 我想我之前应该有提到过--
Oh,and I think I/mentioned this earlier--
你被解雇了
you're fired.
你现在所做的已经越限了
What you did was over the line.
出去
Get out.
但是不要去其他地方
But don't go anywhere.
你还没有被解雇
You're not fired.
暂时没有
Yet.
这件病例中不许炒人
No one is firing anyone/in the middle of this case.
只要摄制组还在
not while those cameras are here,
更何况Taub是这个父亲唯一信任的人
and not while taub is the only/person that this father trusts.
你要去哪里?
where are you going?
去做在这种形势下我一直做的事情--
to do what I always do/in these situations--
用不诚实的方式治疗我的病人
treat my patient behind his back.
这是一个选择
that's one option.
或者你可以给这个孩子的头部/做一个CT扫描
or you can do a ct/scan of the kid's head.
如果没有出现脑中线偏移/那么Taub所说的就是错的
if there's no midline/shift,we know taub was wrong,
你去争取他父亲的同意让孩子/可以使用类固醇
and you get your consent/to give the kid steroids.
这只是一个警告
just a warning.
现在我们做一个治疗 都要取得同意
we have to start getting consent/every time we do a procedure,
不久的将来 他们会要求知情同意
soon they'll be asking/for informed consent.
没想到你还挺有种 敢策划政变
didn't think you had/the guts to stage a coup.
政变失败了
coup failed.
我将在破晓时分被执行死刑
i'm scheduled for execution at dawn.
不 你不会的
no,you're not.
州长不会要求缓刑
no reprieve from the governor.
只要拿到检查结果 你就是他的爱将
you're a test result away from/becoming house's frontrunner.
他不关心你五分钟前说了做了什么
he doesn't care about what you said/or what you did five minutes ago.
他只想要下一个更好的想法
he just wants the next good idea.
把前脑部分放大20%
show me 20% magnification/of the forebrain.
看着我们的病人...
I look at our patient...
看到他的脸的那一刻
soon as I saw his face,
我看见的是正常的孩子
I saw a regular kid.
作为一名整形医生--
one thing about being/a plastic surgeon--
你见到的不是现在的它/而是它可以变成什么
you don't see what/is,you see what could be.
你试试看在House身边这么说话
you talk like that around house,
你能提出多少好的想法都没用
doesn't matter how many/good ideas you come up with.
那么.../告诉我你对自己有什么不满意的地方
so...tell me what you/don't like about yourself.
天啦 呃...有太多地方了
gosh,uh...there's so many things.
呃 Taub医生有空吗?
uh,is Dr. Taub available?
有人跟我推荐过他
because he was very highly recommended.
他已经不在我们诊所了
well,he's no longer practicing with us,
不过我接手了他所有的案子
but I've taken over all his fi
所以如果你告诉我需要做些什么--
so if you tell me/what needs work--
你知道他为什么离开吗?
do you know why he left?
他有些个人问题需要处理/所以如果我们可以--
he had personal issues to/deal with,so if we could just--
噢 我的上帝 他还好吗?
oh,my goodness. is he okay?
是的 他很好
oh,yeah,he's fine.
因为我朋友的耳朵也是他整的
'cause my friend had his/ears done by Dr. Taub.
会不会出问题?
should he worry that/they may...pop back?
不 他不是事故离职的
no,it wasn't a professional issue.
我很抱歉我不能透露更多细节了
i'm sorry I really can't/go into more detail.
我们要不要讨论你的问题?
shall we discuss yourneeds?
你知道大脚趾旁边的那个脚趾吗?
you know that toe next to the big toe?
比我的大脚趾还要大
mine's bigger than my big toe.
有没有什么办法可以让它变短呢?
is there any way to shorten it?
或者让我的大脚趾更大些/例如什么脚趾增大术?
or make my big toe/bigger,like a toe-gmentation?
他是不是撒谎了? 作弊了? 或者偷窃?
did he lie,cheat,or steal?
你不是想整容吧?
you're not here for a/consultation,are you?
怎么看出来的?
what gave me away?
是我那明显完美的脚吗?
was it my obviously perfect feet?
嗨
hi.
CT显示--
ct/shows--
我们走吧
let's go.
你们俩在这做什么?
what are you two doing here?
跳过以下三个场景
skipping three scenes.
CT结果出来了
ct's back.
他会说有脑结构异常的证据
he's gonna say that there's/evidence of an anomaly.
而我会说他错了
i'm gonna say he's wrong.
他又会回去找孩子的父亲
he's gonna go back to the father,
然后回到这个场景
and we'll all end up here.
病变推挤右额叶
defect is pushing on/the right frontal lobe.
这条弧形的变形就是脑疝的征象
this bend is a sign of herniation.
或者是青少年类风湿性关节炎/导致的颅内压升高的征象
or it's a sign of/increased pressure from jra.
Taub医生会干扰你远离真相
dr. Taub would rather/distract you from the truth
用一些闪闪发光的东西/比如说4克拉的钻石
with sparkly things/like 4-carat diamonds.
House
house.
你的合伙人说你因为个人原因离开
your partner said that you/left for personal reasons.
但是你的妻子说你失去了一个病人
but your wife said you lost a patient.
狗娘养的 你跟我妻子说话了?
son of a bitch. you spoke to my wife?
瞧 这就让我困惑了
see,that confused me.
为何给老婆送钻石呢?
why would you give her a diamond
你上的明明是另外一个人
if you screwed somebody else over?
如果你上的是老婆 我可以理解--
if you screwedherover,I/mean,I could--
把摄像机弄出去
get that camera out of here.
你有跟她说了什么没?
you say anything to her?
只是问了问题
just asked questions.
把他们也赶出去
get them out of here too.
我们是医生
we're doctors.
我跟一个护士搞上了
I screwed around with a nurse.
越陷越深
it became a deal.
我的合伙人发现了/于是我辞职
my partners found out,and I resigned.
就这些 高兴啦?
there. Happy?
如果你愿意描述得更多 我会更高兴
if you could be a bit more/descriptive,i'd be happier.
有些人吃止疼药上瘾
some people pop pain pills.
我对妻子不忠
I cheat.
我们都有自己的罪恶
we all have our vices.
Taub
taub.
片子上看不出
I don't see it.
不要去打扰那父子俩
stay away from the family.
House 开始用类固醇 还有/不要去打扰那父子俩
house,start steroids,and/stay away from his family.
哇 你真丑陋
wow. You are ugly.
哇 你真混蛋
wow, you're an ass.
我这叫畸形
I have a deformity.
我知道 所以你才丑
I know. That's why you're ugly.
不过你是个幸运的男孩
but you're a lucky boy.
换作是在动物王国的话
anywhere else in the animal kingdom,
你的父母会在你出生的时候就把你吃掉
your parents would/have eaten you at birth.
你的儿子需要类固醇
your son needs steroids.
Cuddy医生同意了
dr. Cuddy agrees.
Taub医生呢?
does Dr. Taub?
他...他不是一个真正的医生
he's...not a real doctor.
他是整形外科医师
he's a plastic surgeon.
他所关心的只是你的儿子/躺在棺材里好看不
all he cares is that your/son looks good in his coffin.
因此我应该相信你
so I'm supposed to believe you.
真正关心的医生
the doctor who cares.
由我来操心 你就不需要操心了
you shouldn't care if I care.
我不相信你
I don't trust you.
因为我觉得整容不重要?
because I don't think/the surgery's important?
你只相信那些认为整容很重要的人
you're putting your trust in someone/who does think the surgery's important.
你宁愿为了那些他本不需要的事情
you're willing to take chances,
来碰碰运气 拿他的生命来冒险
to risk his life for/something he doesn't need.
我确实需要
I do need it.
我不能谈恋爱
I can't have real relationships.
我甚至不能有一次真实的交谈
I can't even have a real conversation.
甚至包括我的爸爸
not even with my dad.
爸爸...我知道你爱我
dad...I know you love me.
但是你没有把我当作正常人来对待
but you don't treat me normal.
你总是在保护我
you're always protective.
为了我可以诅咒整个世界
the world can always go to hell.
但是你从未对我吼过...
but you never yell at me...
即使我做错事
even wheniscrew up.
我想要做正常人
I wanna be normal.
服用类固醇以后
take your steroids.
你就可以活下来
you get to live.
然后你就能做你的整形手术
then you can do your surgery.
但是那只能改变你的脸
and it'll only change your face.
不能改变这张脸所塑造的你
it won't change who your face made you.
我们会被抓的
we're gonna get caught.
电影里不会的
not on film.
他们所有的摄像设备都在这里
all their camera equipment's in here.
你从哪里得到他们的钥匙的?
where did you get those keys?
Blue 那个清洁工
blue,the janitor.
什么?
what?
那是他的名字
that's his name.
他的名字是Lou
his name's lou.
我欠他一个道歉
owe him an apology.
只看20分钟
just watch 20 minutes of the stuff.
如果我发疯了 记得告诉我
tell me if i'm out of my mind.
我们终于有视频证据了
finally,we have video evidence.
House医生 心脏传导阻滞加肝脏衰竭/可能意味着自身免疫疾病
dr. House,heart block plus liver/failure could mean autoimmune,
或许是硬皮病
maybe scleroderma.
foreman 这么说有道理吗?
foreman,does that make sense?
除非病人手部皮肤变硬/肌肉虚弱
not without tight skin on/the hands, muscle weakness,
年龄超过30岁
and a 30-year-old/patient.
我能再看一遍吗?
can I see that again?
你漏掉什么了吗?
what did you miss?
她说蠢话 我没有--
she screwed/up. I didn't--
不 上半身前倾的那段
no,just the part where/she leans forward.
能看穿她的衣服
I think you can see through her dress.
上消化道出血
upper gi bleed.
也许是他吃的了或喝了什么东西
could be from something he ate or drank.
或许是消化性溃疡
maybe a peptic ulcer.
很好
good.
你真觉得那想法很好吗?
you...thought that was a good idea?
我应该怎么做?
what am I gonna do?
好好享受吧
just enjoy.
我应该因为她把我变成白痴而留下她吗?
i'm gonna keep her around/because she makes me an idiot?
有人能点醒你
well,you're protected.
Foreman不为美色所迷惑
foreman seems immune.
你觉得他是同性恋吗?
you think he's gay?
他在Chase身边有变成白痴吗?
did he become an idiot around chase?
鼻咽血管纤维瘤
nasopharyngeal angiofibroma.
我只是说那不是鼻咽肿瘤
I just said it's not a nasal tumor.
等等  倒下带
wait a minute. rewind that.
她是13吗?
was thatthirteen?
我无法相信我就是那个家伙
I can't believe i'm that guy.
每个人都是那样的家伙
every guy is that guy.
我可不是普通人
i'm not every guy.
咬文嚼字吗?
what,is this semantics here?
好吧-- 所有人都是那样子
okay-- all guys/are that guy.
我不是所有人
i'm not all guys.
Cameron 是聪明的
cameron was smart.
我已经...开始怀疑了
you know,I'm...beginning to doubt that.
我想澄清一下之前说过的话--
I wanted to clarify/something I said earlier--
我说"我爱House医生"
"i love Dr. House."
然后我解释了 那其实是指/"我喜欢和他在一起"
and then I qualified/it,which,after thinking about it,
当然 现在看来
I didn't really need to do.
其实我没必要解释
I didlovebeing around him.
总之 我只是想解释一下之前的解释...
I guess I just wanted to/qualify what I qualified before.
解释等于掩饰 是吧?
i'm looking defensive,aren't i?
不不 我觉得很好
no,no,I think that's great.
全部都解释清楚了
clears everything up.
仅此而已 真的
it's no big deal,really.
左前颞叶有大面积损伤 并伴有水肿
there's a mass lesion in the left/anterior temporal lobe surrounded by edema.
你在用密语侮辱我的智慧吗?/(pig latin: 故意颠倒字母顺序拼凑成的行话)
did you just insult me in pig latin?
拜托 House医生
dr. House,please.
请看一看这个
would you just take a look at this?
病变导致这里出现了结节状阴影
the defect is causing/this nodular shadow here.
看见了吗?
you see it?
你说的对
you're right.
之前我忽略了这一点
I didn't see that before.
好 我们走吧
come on,let's go.
嘿
hey.
我知道你感觉好点了 所以以为自己没事
I know you think you're feeling/better on account of feeling better.
但你们信任的这位家庭医生/认为他发现了一个肿块
but this trusted family doctor/thinks that he's found a mass lesion.
所以拜托你躺下来 假装呼吸困难--
so if you could lie back/down and struggle to breathe--
好吧
okay.
你说对了
you were right.
我很高兴我错了
i'm thrilled I'm wrong.
这太好了 Kenny
this is great,kenny.
你可以做手术了
you're gonna get your surgery now.
到时我第一个要见的人就是你
first person i'm coming/back to see is you.
因为跟我比起来 你会很难看
'cause compared to me,you're/gonna look like butt.
嘿
hey.
怎么 不回嘴吗?
what,no comeback?
看见了没
look at that.
什么?
what?
他的小拇指
his little finger.
有痉挛
it's twitching.
没有啊
no,it's not.
再等等
just give it a second.
看
there.
又如何?
and?
他并未好转
he's not better.
那里出错了?
what's wrong?
我的诊断
my diagnosis.
我不知道他得了什么
I don't know what he has.
取消手术
cancel the surgery.
新症状
new symptom.
无意识的肌肉抽搐
involuntary muscle movement.
手指抽搐也是症状?
a twitching finger is a symptom?
身体出现了不应该出现的反应
the body doing something/it's not supposed to do
这就是症状的定义
is the definition of a symptom.
这手术会改变他的人生
kid's about to have a/life-changing operation.
紧张而已
he's nervous.
也许不是
or he's not.
也许你是对的
or you were right.
类固醇使他情况好转
the kid got better when/we put him on steroids.
他得的是JRA 现在已经控制住了
this is jra,and it's under control now.
或许类固醇仅仅缓和了他的症状
or the steroids have just/tempered his condition.
剪短头发并不能改善发质
he had a haircut,still got bad hair.
莱姆病呢?
what about lyme disease?
符合所有症状 -- 心脏衰竭 内出血
it explains everything-- the/heart issues,internal bleeding,
而且类固醇也可以使之改善
even why it'd get better on steroids.
如果是莱姆病的话
on the other hand,if/he has lyme disease,
应该会出现一些其他的细微症状
there would be other subtle clues,
比如大面积的环状红斑
like a huge,target-shaped rash.
谢谢参与
but thanks for playing.
你为什么不干脆承认/你已经治好了这孩子?
why can't you just accept the/fact that you cured this kid?
你想阻止他的手术
you want to stop his surgery.
你自己不正常 也不希望别人正常
you're not normal,so you don't/want anybody else to be normal.
你觉得正常是不正常的
you don't think normal's healthy.
也许是风湿热
could be rheumatic fever.
也可以被类固醇有效控制
also explains why the steroids helped.
与莱姆病类似的炎症性疾病
it's a similar inflammatory disease.
风湿热不会导致肝功能衰竭
rheumatic fever doesn't/explain liver failure.
Taub认为是那头疼药引起的
taub thinks that acetaminophen does.
好吧 来检验一下你的理论
fine. Let's test your theory.
去掉起搏电极
remove his pacing wire.
如果他有好转 心脏可以自己跳动
if he's better,his heart'll/beat just fine on its own,
那么就可以继续手术
and then he can have his operation.
如果我是对的话 他的心跳将会停止
if I'm right,his heart will stop.
Kutner 去准备除颤器
kutner,have the paddles on standby.
有机会电人了
another chance to blow someone up.
会有些小小的不适
there'll be some minor discomfort,
我会缓慢而稳定的把它拉出来
and you'll feel a/slow,steady pulling sensation.
你确信他的心脏会没事吗?
are you sure his heart/is ready for this?
当然
absolutely.
他相信他是对的
he's convinced he's sure.
不过呢...我很关心你的儿子
whereas...I care about your son
所以我带来一位专业级的心电除颤师
and have, therefore,brought/a professional defibrillist.
不会发生的
we're not gonna need those.
爸 我没事
dad,I feel fine.
我的手指早就不抽搐了
my finger hasn't moved in a while.
好吧
okay.
拉出来
take him off.
开始了
here we go.
心率每分钟85
heart rate's 85 beats per minute.
血压110 / 70
bp 110 over 70.
他怎么样?
is he okay?
没有变化
I feel the same.
他没事
he's fine.
你没事
you're fine.
感谢上帝!
thank god!
什么感谢上帝
what do you mean,thank god?
就是上帝害他搞成这样的
god's the guy who gave it to him.
谢谢
thank you.
可以解释一下手术过程吗?
can you tell us about the procedure?
我们会同时从颅外及颅内
we have to use both an extra/and intracranial approach
切除膨出物
to get enough exposure to/reduce the encephalocele cyst
并进行颅骨修复
and do the bony reconstruction.
你会负责哪一项内容呢?
and how are you participating/in the procedure?
她不参加
she's not.
他们不让我参加/因为他们觉得这孩子已经没事了
they don't want me here,/because they think the kid'***
我不这么想
I don't.
那你认为是什么问题?
and what do you think the problem is?
我也不知道
wish I knew.
我只知道如果House的判断正确
I just know that if Dr. House is right,
手术会出事的
something's gonna go wrong.
House自己都不确定
dr. House doesn't think he's right.
那我最多只是浪费几个小时观察手术
well,then,I'll just waste a/few hours watching a surgery.
比较棘手的是 从这里一直到颅底都需要修复
the danger is we have to reconstruct/all the way down to the cranial base.
这里有些大血管
and there are some/big vessels down there.
所以 我们必须得--
so what we'll do is we'll/work our way down to here--
这些片子是什么时候拍的?
when were these pictures taken?
大约...三周前吧
about...three weeks ago.
怎么了 有问题?
why? What do you see?
这里出现了棘皮病症状
the acanthosis nigricans/was already there.
很早前就有了
it's been there a lot longer than that.
也许已经跟了他一辈子
probably his whole life.
可发际线那里呢?
what about around his hairline?
什么? 那里没有变色现象
what? There's no discoloration.
现在有了
there is now.
我有新理论
I have a new theory.
观点愚蠢并不表示他们智商低下
their bad ideas don't indicate/a lack of intelligence.
这说明思维开放
it indicates an open mind,
他们不局限于传统的--
the willingness not to be/trapped by conventional--
你有麻烦了
you've got a problem.
欢迎指教
tell me something I don't know.
你雇佣漂亮美眉
you hire beautiful girls,
奴役她们 强迫她们留在你身边
enslave them, force/them to be around you,
因为你不知道如何去维系真正的恋情
because you don't know how to/have an actual relationship.
如果她们合格 就留下来
if they're qualified,keep them.
否则就让她们走人 然后再泡
if not,fire them and ask them out.
"欢迎指教"只是客套话而已
you do realize that "tell me something/I don't know" is just an expression.
13号 --
thirteen--
你认为她很漂亮 所以...
you think that just because/she's as beautiful,ergo...
她得不出什么有见地的结论--
you think that because she/hasn't had a decent idea--
不 我的意思是她正在往这走
no,my point is she's/about to enter your office,
你赶快闭嘴
so you should shut up.
你的诊断是对的
you were right about the diagnosis.
没错 幼年类风湿关节炎 我真自豪
yes. It was jra. i'm very proud.
不 我是说 你确实错了
no,I mean you were/right about being wrong.
他得的是莱姆病 所有症状都符合
he's got lyme disease./it explains everything.
你可以晃晃手指吗
could you just hold up some fingers
我想知道自己是不是真瞎了
so I can see if I'm literally blind?
我们早就排除了莱姆病
we ruled out lyme disease hours ago.
所有症状都符合
all the symptoms fit.
我太丢人了
I am so ashamed.
她真的有这么漂亮吗?
is she really that good-looking?
很显然
apparently.
真是红颜祸水啊
how many lives have been/lost because of pretty girls?
那些红斑很隐蔽
the target rash is hiding.
没有人近距离观察过
no one ever looked/at him closely enough.
突然间她没那么红颜了
she's getting uglier by the second.
我们可以假装淡然视之
we can try and pretend we're above it.
我们可以故做理智
we can try and intellectualize it away,
但说到底 光鲜亮丽的东西总是好的
but ultimately,shiny,pretty,perky/things are good,
而丑陋畸形的青年则另人生厌
and ugly,misshapen/teenage boys are repulsive.
我的问题是 Cuddy医生的行政干预使你反感吗?
the question was do you resent Dr./Cuddy's interference in your practice?
呃 似乎我有点答非所问了
well,then I guess my answer/wasn't very helpful,was it?
小种马请起立
mini-stud,stand up.
我和你的另一个合伙人谈过了
I spoke to your other partner.
- Cuddy不是让你--/- 我离的很远
- after cuddy told you--/- no,I stayed away.
我打电话的
did it all over the phone.
我说你在应征整形医生的职位/所以来电咨询
I asked for a reference, said you were/applying for a plastic surgery job.
哦 老天!
oh,god!
没错
yeah.
他暴跳如雷
he went nuts.
很显然 你签署了竞业禁止协议
apparently,you signed a non-compete.
你为什么那么做?
now,why would you agree to that?
我不想再干整形了
I don't wanna practice plastic surgery.
不 是有人逼你那么做的
no. You sign a contract/because someone's making you.
他让你放弃了事业
someone's getting something from you.
你得到了什么回报?
what did they give you in return?
他们答应不说出来
they agreed to keep their mouths shut.
你放弃自己的事业就是为了息事宁人?
so you gave up your chosen/career just so they'd be quiet?
我爱我的太太
I love my wife.
你在没有退路的情况下 还敢和我顶撞?
and you risked this job/with nothing to fall back on?
我以为你错了
I thought you were wrong.
坐下
sit back down.
因为他到处乱搞所以可以留下?
you're keeping him/because he's a philander?
那我呢?
where do I sign up?
去问这个摩门教徒
ask the mormon.
我留着他是因为他好玩
i'm keeping him because/he's interesting.
Terzi医生 请站起来好吗?
dr. Terzi,would you please stand up?
不错
nice.
我对待你有失公平
I have treated you unfairly.
有点先入为主
prejudged you.
为了我的人品起见 我必须纠正错误
and for me to be a better person,/I have to rectify that situation.
你被解雇了
you're fired.
你想...一起吃晚餐吗?
you wanna...grab some dinner?
或者看场电影?
maybe a movie?
我说真的
seriously.
几天之前 Kenny的病情出现了恶化
just days ago,with kenny's/condition worsening,
正是Gregory House医生/使这对父子恢复了信心
it was Dr. Gregory house/reassuring kenny and his father.
我在乎你的孩子
I care about your son.
这位迷人的医生兼电影迷
the charming house,
内心对儿童充满了无微不至的关爱
who happens to be a film buff with a/soft spot in his heart for children,
是什么让他走上从医之道的呢?
told us how he got his start.
我因为这部电影立志当医生
see,I became a doctor because/of the moviepatch adams.
他下定决心要挽救这男孩的生命...
determined to save the boy's life...
真恐怖...
the horror...
还不错啦 他们送了份预览拷贝来
well,it's nice of them/to send us an early copy.
其实是偷来的
not so much sent as stolen.
所以 Gregory不仅仅是一个医生
in the end,it was Dr. Gregory house/who served as not only a doctor,
他更是支撑Kenny父子信心的基石
but a rock for kenny and his father.
你把希望托付在一个相信手术的医生身上
you're putting your trust in someone/whodoesthink the surgery's important.
- 和许多医生不同 House非常的情绪化/- 上帝啊
- house,one of those rare doctors--wears his heart on his sleeve/- god
我的原意是说他那么做很愚蠢
I was saying that was/astupidthing to do.
真是催人泪下啊
it's difficult not to be moved.
得了吧
oh,stop it.
我以后再也不相信Michael Moore的记录片了
suddenly I don't feel like I/can trust michael moore movies.
你去哪?
where are you going?
搭救树上的小猫?
kittens to get out of trees?
还是给失聪的小孩读书?
deaf kids to read to?
我有义务让这邪恶的东西永不见天日
I owe it to the world to make sure/this evil never sees the light of day.
你有什么要说的吗?
anything else,kenny?
谢谢你 House
thank you,Dr. House.
谢谢
thank you.